<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../cas.xsl" ?>
<cas>
    <title>Roots and Shoots</title>
    <advisor>Mr. Vogt</advisor>
    <updated>8/5/2013</updated>
    <imagelist>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>greenclub5.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>greenclub3.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
    </imagelist>
    <content>
        <headline>Activity Overview</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <main maintype="normal">Roots and Shoots is an indispensible club in the Saint Mary's community, for it facilitates the paper recycling process. Due to some precedent changes, this year (2013~2014), Roots and Shoots will be cooperating with Green Club in the paper collection: We gather baskets filled with paper from every room in the campus. For each collection, we collect nearly 6~8kg of paper, and on average, we have 8 collections annually. Although it depends on the number of members and the amount of papers available, the collection process takes about 30 minutes, followed by 1~1.5hours of paper sorting process.</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Philosophy </headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Group Philosophy</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">Acting as a service group in Roots and Shoots must consider two importances; unity within the group to achieve one goal and have to help the environment. Also, we look forward to spread the awareness of eco-friendly methods and to instill a sense of duty towards our environment in young men.&amp;nbsp;</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&amp;nbsp;</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Past Activities</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Paper Collection 2</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">Our most recent collection was held on the 16th of January. This collection consisted of 12 of our original Roots 6 Shoots members, with the support of around 5~6 Green Club members. The collection started as soon as all the last classes ended. We managed to collect the baskets from every classes in the 2nd &amp;amp; the 3rd floor, separating the various types of papers into different bags. The collection ended in an hour, with all the bags of paper ready to be sent to the recycling facility. We resulted in the collection of 18 bags, each bags weighing about 1kg. Our next scheduled collection will be on either the last week of February or the starting week of March. We our expecting to have more members, with a volunteering support from a couple of 6th graders and a increasing amount of our members as well. We will be having a full collection, collecting the baskets from the entire school.</main>
        </subcontent>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Paper Collection</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">So far, we've had two paper recycling sessions. The collections were successful not only because there are increased number of members (Green Club and Roots and Shoots), but also because everyone cooperated well with each other. We are looking forward to have another paper recycling session soon.&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Members 2013~2014</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Officers</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;President&lt;/strong&gt;- Taichi Shimizu (11)</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;Vice-President&lt;/strong&gt;- Denny Someya (12)&amp;nbsp;</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;Secretary&lt;/strong&gt;- Anthony Peraro (12)</main>
        </subcontent>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Other Members</subheadline>
            <main maintype="list">Mokhtar Ali Yamani</main>
            <main maintype="list">Juhan Bae</main>
            <main maintype="list">Sung Mo Koo</main>
            <main maintype="list">Hanbie Lee</main>
            <main maintype="list">Marx Kamiyama</main>
            <main maintype="list">Stephan NItu</main>
            <main maintype="list">Tetsuo Kobayashi</main>
            <main maintype="list">Seung Hyo Chang</main>
            <main maintype="list">Min Ho Kim</main>
            <main maintype="list">Mailen Trout</main>
            <main maintype="list">Yuuki Wood</main>
            <main maintype="list">Tajinder Singh</main>
            <main maintype="list">Lucas Shiraki</main>
            <main maintype="list">Khalid Saifullah</main>
            <main maintype="list">Sang Soo Na</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
</cas>
