<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../cas.xsl" ?>
<cas>
    <title>Student Council</title>
    <advisor>Counsellor</advisor>
    <updated>8/5/2013</updated>
    <imagelist>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>studentcouncil1.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>studentcouncil2.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>studentcouncil3.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
    </imagelist>
    <content>
        <headline>Activity Overview</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <main maintype="normal">The Student Council fulfils an integral role in the St. Mary?fs Community, acting as the predominant liaison between the students and the administrators of the school. Representing the entire student body of St. Mary?fs, the Student Council works on a variety of initiatives that help enrich student life. While such initiatives vary greatly from year to year, throughout the 2013-14 school year the Student Council has attempted to raise funds to support the refurnishing of student lounges, increase school spirit through a variety of events and activities, and instigate awareness of world events through charity drives.&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Group Philosophy</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>List of Initiatives for 2013 ~ 2014</subheadline>
            <main maintype="list">Excursions for All Grade Levels</main>
            <main maintype="list">Senior Privileges</main>
            <main maintype="list">Lounge Reformation</main>
            <main maintype="list">Sales of Titans Merchandise</main>
            <main maintype="list">Tri- School Movie Night</main>
            <main maintype="list">Tri- School Dance</main>
            <main maintype="list">Tri- School Prom</main>
            <main maintype="list">Spirit Day</main>
            <main maintype="list">Career Day</main>
            <main maintype="list">December 1 Million Yen Charity Drive for Tacloban, Philippines</main>
            <main maintype="list">Facebook Weekly Shoutouts</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Responsibilities</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">The members of the Student Council have biweekly meetings from 11:00-12:00, primarily discussing future and past events, resource allocation, and general suggestions that non-Student Council members have. As the Student Council represents a prestigious collection of elected individuals, members are expected to wholeheartedly commit to the Student Council and voluntarily support the aforementioned initiatives.&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Election Process</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>How the representatives are chosen</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">Student Council representatives are voted at the end of the previous school year. Candidates who run for Executive positions must speak before the entire High School student body and are henceforth chosen through school-wide ballots. Class Presidents and Class Representatives must submit a 150-word blurb and are henceforth chosen through grade-wide ballots.&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Members 2015~2016</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Student Council Executive Board</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;President&lt;/strong&gt;- Wilson Zhang (12)</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;Vice- President&lt;/strong&gt;- Matthew Liao (12)</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;Secretary&lt;/strong&gt;- Jun Woo Hwang (11)&amp;nbsp;</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;Treasurer&lt;/strong&gt;- Hee Do Chung (12)&amp;nbsp;</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Past Events</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Christmas Concert</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">On December 7th and 8th, St.Mary's held the annual Christmas concerts at the ES and HS level for both instrumental and choral divisions. As student council representatives, we promoted donations to the Philippines and asked for some money at the concerts. Grade representatives went around the audience passing around some bags, and after the collection, we were amazed at how much we were able to collect. Jae Yoon, Mackenzie, and Kazuya also made a speech at the beginning of each concert, generally asking for donations to reach our benchmark of 1 million yen. Through the sales of Christmas grams, bake sales, ES sharing boxes, athletics sales, and general donations, we were able to collect over 1 million yen, attaining our goals before the end of 2013. The spirit of giving has permeated the student body, and students as well as faculty members united to donate towards the victims of the typhoon in the Philippines.&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Movie Night</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">On November 21st, the student council held the first ever movie night in the band room. This was a social even where students were encouraged to sit in the band room with some snacks to watch a movie. Each student paid 300 yen to enter and watch the movie. From 5pm to 6:45pm was the first movie, and the second movie ran from7pm to 9om. The first movie was called the Intouchables and the second one was called Now You See Me. They were both amazing movies and the audience had mentioend it was an enjoyable evening, and our sales at the concessions stand were also very fruitful. We plan to hold this event again because there is no cost in running this event, except buying the DVD's, which is much cheaper than hosting a dance party. Ms. Reynolds was very cooperative in this idea, and she was also content with how there was no mes left over in the band room. It was the first time that the student council hosted this event, so the high school administration was also very delighted with this idea. Booking and arranging of the room took some time, but other than that, everything went smoothly and we wish to host another one in the near future.&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
</cas>
