<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../cas.xsl" ?>
<cas>
    <title>Musical</title>
    <advisor></advisor>
    <updated>6/22/2013</updated>
    <imagelist>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>2015_04_15_1382.JPG</image>
            <caption>Spring Musical Little Shop of Horrors</caption>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>2015_04_15_01382.JPG</image>
            <caption>Spring Musical Orchestra 2014</caption>
        </imagegroup>
    </imagelist>
    <content>
        <headline>Activity Overview</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <main maintype="normal">The Spring Musical is an interscholastic activity, featuring students from St. Mary's International School (SMIS), International School of the Sacred Heart (ISSH), and Seisen International School (SIS).  It is the biggest theatre event of the school year. Every year, musicians, artists, and actors collaborate to produce a magnificent production, each contributing to the musical by playing the musical orchestra, being a part of the painting crew, being a member of the costumes and makeup crew, helping with the lighting, publicising the event, or, of course, singing. Whether onstage or backstage, there are many opportunities to get involved. The musical is a creative and wholesome way to utilize one's talents.</main>
<main maintype="normal">Over the past years, we have presented productions ranging from Broadway classics such as Guys and Dolls, Fiddler on the Roof, West Side Story, South Pacific, and Joseph and the Amazing Technicolor Dreamcoat to modern, contemporary productions such as Into The Woods, The 21st Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee and The Little Shop of Horrors. 
</main>
        </subcontent>
         <subcontent>
         <subheadline>Groups</subheadline>
         <main maintype="normal">There are three main groups relating to the musical: Cast, Backstage and Orchestra.</main> 

<main maintype="normal">Cast: Auditions for acting and the musical orchestra will be held sometime the end of November.  Students wishing to perform as a cast member must have a high level of proficiency in both acting and singing. Parts are assigned according to the roles needed for that particular musical; the exact parts differ each year. The audition is quite competitive, and members must pledge to be fully committed once earning a role as a cast member. Rehearsals begin from the beginning of the second semester and run from 4:30-7:00pm on weekdays.  Performances are held in the second week of April. Rehearsals may get extended as the performance dates approach. For details please contact Mr. Stenson (SMIS Fine Arts coordinator).</main>

<main maintype="normal">Backstage: This group manages a wide range of necessary tasks to support the cast, such as the cast makeup, costume design, publicity, stage props, stage setup and painting, sound systems and lighting. This group usually requires many people and is not as competitive as the cast. Students are asked to come several times a week, but the exact schedules tend to be somewhat flexible compared to those of the cast.</main>

<main maintype="normal">Orchestra: The orchestra consists of strings, winds and some percussion. The exact instrumentation varies from year to year. Students interested must see Ms. Reynolds (SMIS band director) at some point before January. There is a simple auditioning process for the orchestra to check for a basic level of proficiency. Some parts tend to be more competitive than others, and those who received parts must be fully committed to the musical.</main>
</subcontent>
<subcontent>
		 <subheadline>2015 Musical: Dirty Rotten Scoundrels</subheadline>
		  <main maintype="normal">Performance dates: April 17, 18 and 19

“Lawrence Jameson makes his lavish living by talking rich ladies out of their money. Freddy Benson more humbly swindles women by waking their compassion with fabricated stories about his grandmother’s failing health. After meeting on a train, they attempt to work together only to find that this small French town isn’t big enough for the two of them. They agree on a settlement: the first one to extract $50,000 from a young female target, heiress Christine Colgate, wins and the other must leave town. A hilarious battle of cons ensues that will keep audiences laughing, humming, and guessing to the end!</main>
</subcontent>
<subcontent>
         <subheadline>2014 Musical: Little Shop of Horrors</subheadline>
         <main maintype="normal">The 2014 musical was Little Shop of Horrors, written by Howard Ashman and composed by Alan Menken; premiered in 1982, subsequent Broadway production in 2003.
“Seymour Krelbourn is a poor young man working at a run-down flower shop on skid row when he discovers an alien plant after a total eclipse of the sun. After bringing of the plant to the store, he gains fame, fortune, and love.  The only defect is that the plant feeds on human blood. Seymour and the plant make a deal that, if the plant continues to bring Seymour positive attention, he will in turn continue to feed the plant human bodies…”</main>

<main maintype="normal">The 2014 musical was presented through special agreement with Music Theater International (MTI).
All Authorized performance materials were also supplied by MTI at:</main>
<main maintype="normal">421 West 54th Street</main>
<main maintype="normal">New York, NY 10019</main>
<main maintype="normal">(212) 541-4684</main>
<main maintype="normal">www.mtishow.com.</main>
         </subcontent>
         
    </content>
</cas>
