<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../cas.xsl" ?>
<cas>
    <title>Debate</title>
    <advisor></advisor>
    <updated>6/22/2013</updated>
    <imagelist>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>2_07_2014_1001.JPG</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>2_07_2014_1002.JPG</image>
        </imagegroup>
    </imagelist>
    <content>
        <headline>Activity Overview</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <main maintype="normal">Debate is one of the most active fine arts at St. Mary’s. Practices are held on a weekly to monthly basis on Wednesday nights. After school meetings happen after school every weekday to 5:00PM excepting Wednesdays and Fridays. This extracurricular is not compatible with wrestling, though allowances can be made for overlap in other schedules.</main>
            <main maintype="normal">Operating on the Australian three speaker system, Debate is a perfect opportunity for students to test critical thinking, group skills, eloquence, and rapid thinking as they discuss a certain topic, defending either the affirmative or negative viewpoint. They will have to operate in tandem with their two team members and defend against interjections made during their speech. Four practices and two tournaments are held each year for both Junior Varsity and Varsity.</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
    <subcontent>
<h3>2014~2015 Season</h3><h4>Season Summary</h4><p></p><div style="text-indent: 40px;" class="description">The St. Mary's Debate Team was somewhat inexperienced at the beginning of the season, with only a third of the team having been previously in Varsity, though some experience was claimed by all members. The team rapidly grew and learned from their new environment, and had many great speakers. However, this was not enough to swing the tide in their favour, and they tied with last year's champions, ASIJ, at second place while the unsuspected but strong Seisen team secured their first debate tournament victory in many years at first place. The team grew and learned however, and can expect a fresher and learning group for the coming years. The A Team's third speaker Sung Mo Koo won a speaker award and the same team's first and second speakers, Stefan Nitu and Wilson Zhang, won All-Stars.</div><p></p><h4>Teams and Awards</h4><p></p><div style="text-indent: 40px;" class="description"><strong>A Team</strong></div><p></p><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Stefan Nitu</div></li><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Wilson Zhang</div></li><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Sung Mo Koo</div></li><p></p><div style="text-indent: 40px;" class="description"><strong>B Team</strong></div><p></p><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Dylan Thinnes</div></li><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Tae Jun Seo</div></li><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Raymond Zurich</div></li><p></p><div style="text-indent: 40px;" class="description"><strong>C Team</strong></div><p></p><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Stefano A De Lima</div></li><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Saharsh Abbigani</div></li><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Atharv Patankar</div></li><p></p><div style="text-indent: 40px;" class="description"><strong>All Stars</strong></div><p></p><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Stephan Nitu</div></li><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Wilson Zhang</div></li><p></p><div style="text-indent: 40px;" class="description"><strong>Speaker Awards</strong></div><li style="margin-left:30px;"><div class="description">Sung Mo Koo</div></li>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
</cas>
