<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../cas.xsl" ?>
<cas>
    <title>Fall Play</title>
    <advisor></advisor>
    <updated>6/22/2013</updated>
    <imagelist>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>-1.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>-2.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>-3.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
     </imagelist>
    <content>
        <headline>Activity Overview</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <main maintype="normal">The Fall Play is typically either a mystery or a thriller. Over the past couple of years, we have presented plays such as: Mumbo Jumbo, Don't Drink the Water, The Lady Vanishes, Murder in the Wings, and Catering to Murder. Traditionally, the Fall Play is in the style of a theatre in the round, which allows the audience to view the stage from all four sides. Every year, the Fall Play showcases a talented group of students from St. Mary's International School and Seisen International School. Including students from many different grade levels, the Fall Play develops camaraderie among students who are of different ages, but have similar interests.</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Fall Play 2015</headline>
        <subcontent>
          <main maintype="normal">The Fall Play this year has been postponed indefinitely.</main>
          </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Fall 2014 Season Summary “Casablanca”</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <main maintype="normal">“Casablanca, the Fall Play this year,  is an attempt to take that famous movie back to its little known roots as an unproduced play. This year’s play will go back traditional theatre layout, with the stage being presented in a way reminiscent of a Hollywood film set. The actors, many of whom have been in several previous productions, took active roles in the developing of the movie script into that of a workable live play.  Notable this year is the introduction of 10 short musical pieces featuring a live 4 piece-band and, of course, Sam (and Ilsa) at the piano. The backstage crew was incredibly professional and a pleasure to work with. This production belongs to the students.” -Season summary by Mr. Martens, Fall Play Director 2014.</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
   </cas>
