<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../../../cas.xsl" ?>
<cas>
    <title>Green Club</title>
    <advisor>Mrs. D. Kobayashi</advisor>
    <updated>8/5/2013</updated>
    <imagelist>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>greenclub3.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>greenclub4.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>greenclub5.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>umino mori 1.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>umino mori 2.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
        <imagegroup>
            <image>umino mori 5.jpg</image>
        </imagegroup>
    </imagelist>
    <content>
        <headline>Past Activities</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Christmas Ornament Contest Workshop 12/03~12/04</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">Christmas Ornament contest is the biggest activity that the green club hosts annually. The preparation and the organization needed to make this particular activity successful is immense, but because of such invovlement, this activity has been the most meaningful and successful endeavor. The rules are very simple: The elementary students are given a week to complete their ornaments, demonstrating their creativity. The students are given two days in which they can attend the ornament contest workshops, which is exactly the subjects that are being reported now. Then, the green club provides a display on which the ornaments can be hung and be judged. (This year, our judge is on the 9th or December) Then, the ornaments are displayed for 2~3 days: During that time, people can choose to buy the ornaments. The fund raised in this activity will then be proceeded to buy the prizes for award-winning ornaments. From the observations made during the workshop, it seems that we have some great entries this year!</main>
        </subcontent>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Carnival Green Club Booth</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">Green club has been the official member of the SMIS carnival since last year. The purpose of this activity is to raise a fund to buy prizes for other activies such as the Christmas Ornament Contest. The members of the green club get together three weeks in advance to come up with a game that all the visitors to the carnival can enjoy as well as raise awareness of the importance of protecting the environment. For instance, last year, we created a game where one can thow a garbage into a combustable, non-combustable, or recycle bins (into the right garbage cans) to earn points. If one reaches 100 points, they could get a handful of candies as a prize. This activity is very student directly and each of the members can demonstrate their leadership and creativity.</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>2013 ~ 2014 Schedule</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Future Plans</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">Green Club has been so far successful in the activities that I have taken on. The members of the green club, therefore, want to continue on with the momentum to contribute to the greening of the SMIS community as well as the world. Just last week, Yong Chul Yoon, the leader of Green Club, talked with Ms. Wayne, who had proposed four possible projects we can undertake, to discuss whether or not her proposals are doable in the next couple of months. So, in the next meeting, the club will be deciding which one (or two) of the four choices are feasible.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1) Greening of the school</main>
            <main maintype="normal">2) Educating the young via presentations</main>
            <main maintype="normal">3) Creating lists that can be taped to the garbage can, which should facilitate the source separation&amp;nbsp;</main>
            <main maintype="normal">4) Taking good care of the Brothers' garden</main>
            <main maintype="normal">Along with these, we are still going to do the following, rather traditional, activities.&amp;nbsp;</main>
            <main maintype="normal">1) River Clean ups</main>
            <main maintype="normal">2) Carnival Fundraising&amp;nbsp;</main>
            <main maintype="normal">We look forward to be even more active in the following months.&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Activity Overview</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <main maintype="normal">Green Club SMIS, is pushing forward trying to achieve the best for the world today. Through as passive approaches as possible we are pushing forward and will be raising the awareness of our dying world and what we can do about it. We will be taking creative steps forward in contests, activities, clean-ups, plantings, or anything else that, rather than posing a threat to humans, will simply just provide a cleaner, safer, and fixed situation, from which we can take another step into saving the environment and protecting our world. We will be involving anyone who may have the motivation and determination, regardless of age or ability, for all you need to protect the environment is passion.</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Aims</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>List of Aims</subheadline>
            <main maintype="list">
 &lt;strong&gt;Its Members&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;We want to make sure our members, take a hands-on-approach in trying to save&amp;nbsp;the environment rather than through other mediums. We want to give them the opportunity to&amp;nbsp;see what our environment is like and make a physical difference by being at the very place they&amp;nbsp;need to be rather than by just spreading awareness. Apart from providing CAS points, we&amp;nbsp;believe the members can also feel like they are making a difference.</main>
            <main maintype="list">&lt;strong&gt;The Other Students in the School&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;We would like high school students to be aware of the&amp;nbsp;environmental issues of today, but basically, for them to have the experiences in making a&amp;nbsp;difference we would like to encourage them to join. However, for the rest of the school, such as&amp;nbsp;the elementary and junior high, we would like them to take part in activities to, which we will&amp;nbsp;be setting up. We would also like to make sure that they are aware.</main>
            <main maintype="list">&lt;strong&gt;The Wider School Community and Beyond&lt;/strong&gt;:&amp;nbsp;Again, awareness is the biggest factor, but in&amp;nbsp;addition, we want to make sure this awareness reaches new levels of realization and lead the&amp;nbsp;other members of society. We want them to try to take action themselves in anyway possible.&amp;nbsp;Green Club SMIS is always there to provide them with means to take a part, but we would like&amp;nbsp;to make sure that people have realized that they can take action themselves. We want the&amp;nbsp;members of society to understand that it is them who live in the environment, on this earth and&amp;nbsp;it is also their duty to save it. We want them to understand that they can take a passive approach&amp;nbsp;and still make a monumental difference.</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Purpose</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <main maintype="normal">Green Club SMIS aims to make sure that our society understands what the world is&amp;nbsp;facing today. We strive to make sure everybody is aware of what our earth is like, our resources becoming&amp;nbsp;scarcer and scarcer every second, the world being littered, The air being polluted, and much much more&amp;nbsp;detrimental situations. We endeavor to make sure everybody is not only aware but also reach realization&amp;nbsp;about these situations and fathom that they, themselves, have the power to make a difference passively. We&amp;nbsp;want people to take action and understand that even their contributions can make a monumental difference.</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Philosophy</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;em&gt;Green Club SMIS, is pushing forward trying to achieve the best for the world today. Through as passive&amp;nbsp;approaches as possible we are pushing forward and will be raising the awareness of our dying world and&amp;nbsp;what we can do about it. We will be taking creative steps forward in contests, activities, clean-ups,&amp;nbsp;plantings, or anything else that, rather than posing a threat to humans, will simply just provide a cleaner,&amp;nbsp;safer, and fixed situation, from which we can take another step into saving the environment and protecting&amp;nbsp;our world. We will be involving anyone who may have the motivation and determination, regardless of age&amp;nbsp;or ability, for all you need to protect the environment is passion.&lt;/em&gt;</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
    <content>
        <headline>Members 2015~2016</headline>
        <subcontent>
            <subheadline>Officers</subheadline>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;Officer&lt;/strong&gt;- Lane Woody (12)</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;Officer&lt;/strong&gt;- Ekamjot Bedi (11)</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;Officer&lt;/strong&gt;- Marius Ruh (12)</main>
            <main maintype="normal">&lt;strong&gt;Officer&lt;/strong&gt;- Juan Borja (12)&amp;nbsp;</main>
        </subcontent>
    </content>
</cas>
